Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
(HORSES WHINNY)
Do not stop until you reach Tartarus
The horses will run
until their hearts give out.
Hyperion will soon have the Bow. Leave.
(PANTING)
(FOOTSTEPS RUMBLING)
Forgive me. Father. Forgive me.
I only broke the law
to protect the mortal.
(SLOW-MOTION SHOUT)
No god will ever again come to your aid.
You are on your own!
Do you understand. mortal?
I have faith in you. Theseus.
Prove me right.
Lead your people.
(SCREECHING)
Halt!
(HORSES SNORTING. PANTING)
(SNARLING)
The horse I prayed for when I was a boy.
What is wrong with him?
They're dying.
Where are the men?
MAN: They have yet to return. sire.
What does the sight
of the bird tell you?
Speak.
The gods.
They came from above.
The gods?
They appeared and laid waste
to the men. my king.
The gods.
They protected the slave
who travels with the oracle.
The gods fight on their behalf. sire.
If the men hear of this.
there will be panic.
I know. I know.
(SQUISHING)
(SCREAMING CONTINUES)
ATHENA: In peace. sons bury their fathers.
In war. fathers bury their sons.
Are we at war. Father?
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
I have important information
for the council.
Theseus.
I know this man. Let him through.
I hope you've come to join the fight.
Where's the army?
Tell me about the slave.
He's from your village. is he not?
- Answer me!
- Yes.
He was a peasant.
As was I.
Forgive me. Your Majesty.
- I meant no...
- Quiet.
And his family?
His mother was raped by some villagers.
Nobody would many her.
He was a bastard.
(THUNDER RUMBLES)
And his name?
Theseus.
Very well. I'll meet him.
Helios tells me you have information
that could be of use to us.
Hyperion is in possession
of the Epirus Bow.
- The Epirus Bow?
- Yes. it's a weapon forged by Heracles.
Oh. please. I heard the same stories
you did as a child.
There are gods living in the clouds.
Titans buried in the rocks.
Listen. I was a disbeliever just like
you are. But the Epirus Bow exists
I understand there are many Hellenics
who put faith in the myths and the gods.
but we on the Hellenic council do not.
They are metaphors. son. Nothing more.
We are a society of laws
based on negotiation and reason.
If you try and negotiate with Hyperion.
you will be the death of us all.
If I were to accept your counsel.
Theseus from Kolpos. what would it be?
Seal the gates and prepare for war.
We have Hoplite battalions returning.
We can't seal the gate.
No one will return! We are the last!
I'm sure you'll understand
if I don't accept the advice
of an alluring palm reader
and her peasant lover.
Sir. a Heraklion envoy approaches.
There. you see? No ruler wishes for war.
They only wish to be taken seriously
at the bargaining table.
Alert the council. Prepare a delegation.
MAN: Bows!
HELIOS: Stop!
Stop! Remain still.
or we'll be forced to fire upon you.
Extend your arms outward.
He bears the olive branch of peace.
HYPERION: My king wishes to speak
to the one called Theseus from Kolpos.
Theseus.
Hyperion's envoy
desires a word with you.
Like the vision.
he sends for you with arms open.
Seeking an embrace of loyalty.
Phaedra.
Have you never been wrong?
We can't protect you beyond this gate.
I am Theseus!
Come closer. I have a message for you.
Don't risk it.
At worst. you lose a peasant.
- Better?
- Uh-huh. Yes.
Why do you cover your face?
All are equal in Hyperion's midst.
I myself am only a vessel
for his demands. Nothing more.
- And he asks me by name?
- Indeed he does.
And how does he know it?
There's little the king does not know.
He knows that you have no father.
And like him. you were cast aside
by your own people.
Does he know of my rage?
Does he know that I live only to see
his blood at the end of my sword?
Does he know he butchered my mother?
Now that he's seen your face. he knows.
You wouldn't make it.
Coward!
Embrace me. Theseus.
They will never give you a seat
at their table
but you could sit at the head of mine.
Long after this war is over. my mark
will be left on this world forever.
The sun will never set
on my blood. Theseus.
This is what I offer you. Immortality.
Deeds are eternal. Not the flesh.
The gods may be on your side.
but tomorrow...
I unleash the Titans.
What was discussed?
Seal the gate.
- What were his demands?
- Seal the gate.
HYPERION: Theseus.
Ahh...
(SHOUTS)
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
- That was him. wasn't it?
- I was that close.
I don't know if I can do
what Zeus asks of me.
By doubting one
comes the truth. Theseus.
The gods chose well.
Sir. there's movement on the front.
What is he holding?
The Bow.
MAN: The commanders
are all dead! Fall back!
(PANICKED SHOUTING)
Hold! Stand your ground!
Listen to me!
Listen!
- Who are you to tell us what to do?
- I am nobody to tell you what to do!
I am Theseus. a common man! One of you!
I share your blood!
And I share your fear!
But to run now would offer our souls
and the souls of our children
to a terrible darkness!
(ALL SHOUTING)
Hold! We must stand and fight!
Their numbers count for nothing
in the tunnel! Stand your ground!
Stand your ground!
Who are they that we are not?
Just because they scald their faces
and scar their bodies...
does not mean they are braver
or stronger than we are.
They are cowards!
They hide behind their masks.
They are human.
and they bleed like you and I.
Listen to me!
Stand your ground!
Fight for honor!
Fight for the man beside you!
Fight for the mothers who bore you!
Fight for your children!
Fight for your future!
Fight so your name survives!
Fight...
for immortality!
Let us write history
with Heraklion blood!
(FOOTSTEPS RUMBLING)
Ready! Move!
(SHOUTS)
(ALL GRUNTING. SHOUTING)
King Hyperion.
We can negotiate. I see no reason...
HYPERION: Theseus!
Here I am! Theseus of Kolpos!
- Where's your king?
- He is no king.
(SHOUTS)
Stavros! The shrine!
Theseus! I'm right behind you!
Phaedra!
Stay in the shrine.
Hyperion!
(SNARLING)
No!
(GRUNTS)
STAVROS (MUFFLED):
Theseus. wake up!
Theseus!
(GROANS)
I got the Bow!
Stavros.
I got the Bow.
Get out of here while you can!
I'll hold them off!
Stavros.
Go now! I got the Bow!
I'll hold them off while I can!
- Get out of here! Go!
- (CREATURES SNARLING)
Which one of you are coming with me?
(SCREAMING)
None of you will leave this place.
(SHOUTS)
Leave here!
This is no longer your fight.
Find Hyperion.
(ALL SNARLING)
(GODS GRUNTING)
(GASPS)
(GRUNTING)
(BOTH SCREAMING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(GROANING)
(PANTING)
Die with your gods.
(BOTH SHOUTING)
(SNARLING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(GRUNTING)
(SHOUTING)
(ALL SHOUTING)
Athena!
(GROANING)
Father!
Don't forsake mankind.
(GRUNTING)
(SIGHS)
What does it feel like. knowing...
knowing that there'll
be no memory of you?
I have won.
My death will make me a legend.
(PANTING)
My deeds...
will go down in history.
I'm writing your history.
(ROARS)
(SCREAMS)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(SCREAMING)
Do it!
(MEN SHOUTING)
This... is our last embrace. Hyperion.
Look at me.
I'm the last thing...
you will ever see.
Witness hell.
(STABBING SOUND)
(GURGLING)
(FADING GROAN)
(ALL SHOUTING)
(SHOUTING. RUMBLING FADES)
OLD MAN: All men's
souls are immortal.
But the souls of the righteous
are immortal and divine.
Once a faithless man.
Theseus gave his life
to save mankind
and earned a place amongst the gods.
They rewarded his
bravery with a gift.
A son. Acamas.
(ARMIES SHOUTING)
(GASPS)
Don't be afraid of your visions.
little one.
- What's your name?
- Acamas.
Acamas.
A strong name.
I knew your father.
He was a very brave man.
Soon. it will be your time
My time for what?
The fight against evil
never ends. Acamas.
War is coming to the heavens.
And your father will be there.
fighting for your future.
PHAEDRA: Acamas.
Acamas.
Who was that. son?
Just...
Just an old man.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(SNARLING)
(ARMIES SHOUTING)
(GASPS. PANTING)
English - US - SDH
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today